
exports.seed = function(knex) {
  // Deletes ALL existing entries
  return knex('flashcard').del()
    .then(function () {
      // Inserts seed entries
      return knex('flashcard').insert([
        { front: 'history1 front', back: 'history1 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history2 front', back: 'history2 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history3 front', back: 'history3 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history4 front', back: 'history4 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history5 front', back: 'history5 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history6 front', back: 'history6 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history7 front', back: 'history7 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history8 front', back: 'history8 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'history9 front', back: 'history9 back', deck_id: 1 },
        { front: 'english1 front', back: 'english1 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'english2 front', back: 'english2 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'english3 front', back: 'english3 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'english4 front', back: 'english4 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'english5 front', back: 'english5 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'english6 front', back: 'english6 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'english7 front', back: 'english7 back', deck_id: 2 },
        { front: 'math1 front', back: 'math1 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math2 front', back: 'math2 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math3 front', back: 'math3 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math4 front', back: 'math4 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math5 front', back: 'math5 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math6 front', back: 'math6 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math7 front', back: 'math7 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math8 front', back: 'math8 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'math9 front', back: 'math9 back', deck_id: 3 },
        { front: 'biology1 front', back: 'biology1 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology2 front', back: 'biology2 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology3 front', back: 'biology3 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology4 front', back: 'biology4 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology5 front', back: 'biology5 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology6 front', back: 'biology6 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology7 front', back: 'biology7 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology8 front', back: 'biology8 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology9 front', back: 'biology9 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology10 front', back: 'biology10 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology11 front', back: 'biology11 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology12 front', back: 'biology12 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology13 front', back: 'biology13 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology14 front', back: 'biology14 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'biology15 front', back: 'biology15 back', deck_id: 4 },
        { front: 'sociology1 front', back: 'sociology1 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology2 front', back: 'sociology2 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology3 front', back: 'sociology3 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology4 front', back: 'sociology4 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology5 front', back: 'sociology5 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology6 front', back: 'sociology6 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology7 front', back: 'sociology7 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology8 front', back: 'sociology8 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology9 front', back: 'sociology9 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'sociology10 front', back: 'sociology10 back', deck_id: 5 },
        { front: 'pscychology1 front', back: 'psychology1 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'pscychology2 front', back: 'psychology2 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'pscychology3 front', back: 'psychology3 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'pscychology4 front', back: 'psychology4 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'pscychology5 front', back: 'psychology5 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'pscychology6 front', back: 'psychology6 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'pscychology7 front', back: 'psychology7 back', deck_id: 6 },
        { front: 'englishTwo1 front', back: 'englishTwo1 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo2 front', back: 'englishTwo2 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo3 front', back: 'englishTwo3 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo4 front', back: 'englishTwo4 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo5 front', back: 'englishTwo5 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo6 front', back: 'englishTwo6 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo7 front', back: 'englishTwo7 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo8 front', back: 'englishTwo8 back', deck_id: 7 },
        { front: 'englishTwo9 front', back: 'englishTwo9 back', deck_id: 7 },
      ]);
    });
};
